spaceelephant.com 2009-12-20

# Space Elephant

### Our Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

We may also share your personal information with:

            Members of the SpaceElephant.com, Inc. corporate family to provide joint content and services (like registration, transactions and customer support), to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and violations of our policies, and to guide decisions about their products, services and communications. Members of our corporate family will use this information to send you marketing communications only if you’ve requested their services. 

            Service providers under contract who help with our business operations (such as fraud investigations, bill collection, affiliate and rewards programs and co-branded credit cards). 

            Other third parties to whom you explicitly ask us to send your information (or about whom you are otherwise explicitly notified and consent to when using a specific service). 

            Law enforcement or other governmental officials, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity. In such events, we will disclose information relevant to the investigation, such as name, city, state, zip code, telephone number, email address, User ID history, IP address, fraud complaints, and bidding and listing history. 

            SpaceElephant.com in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. In such events, we will disclose name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email address and company name. 

            Other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity. (Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information. If your personal information will be used contrary to this policy, you will receive prior notice.) 

Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.

### Privacy

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. We use your information only as described in the SpaceElephant Privacy Policy. We view protection of users' privacy as a very important community principle. We store and process your information on computers located in the United States and Canada that are protected by physical as well as technological security devices. You can access and modify the information you provide us and choose not to receive certain communications by signing in to your account. We use third parties to verify and certify our privacy principles. 

### Indemnity

You will indemnify and hold us (and our officers, directors, agents, subsidiaries, joint ventures, and employees) harmless from any claim or demand, including reasonable attorneys' fees, made by any third party due to or arising out of your breach of this Agreement, or your violation of any law or the rights of a third party.

### No Agency

No agency, partnership, joint venture, employee-employer, or franchiser-franchisee relationship is intended or created by this Agreement.

### Information You Share on SpaceElephant

Your User ID is displayed throughout SpaceElephant.com (and so available to the public), and is connected to all of your SpaceElephant.com activity. Other people can see your purchases, items for sale, storefronts, feedback, ratings and associated comments. Notices sent to other community members about suspicious activity and policy violations on our sites refer to User IDs and specific items. So if you associate your name with your User ID, the people to whom you have revealed your name will be able to personally identify your SpaceElephant.com activities.

If you access our sites from a shared computer or a computer in an internet café, certain information about you, such as your User ID, activity or reminders from SpaceElephant.com, may also be visible to other individuals who use the computer after you.

### Using Information from SpaceElephant.com

SpaceElephant.com enables you to share personal and financial information to complete transactions. We encourage you to disclose your privacy practices and respect the privacy of other users. We cannot guarantee the privacy or security of your information and therefore we encourage you to evaluate the privacy and security policies of your trading partner before entering into a transaction and choosing to share your information. To help protect your privacy, we allow only limited access to other users' contact, shipping and financial information to facilitate your transactions. When users are involve d in a transaction, they may have access to each other's name, User ID, email address and other contact and shipping information. In all cases, you mu st give other users a chance to remove themselves from your database and a chance to review what information you have collected about the m.

You agree to use user information only for:

            SpaceElephant.com transaction-related purposes that are not unsolicited commercial messages; 

            using services offered through SpaceElephant.com ( _e.g._ escrow, insurance, shipping and fraud complaints), or 

            other purposes that a user expressly chooses.

### Account Protection

Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not disclose your SpaceElephant.com password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify SpaceElephant.com and change your password.

### Security

Your information is stored on our servers located in the United States and Canada. We treat data as an asset that must be protected and use lots of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the site. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

### Third Parties

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to others, whether they are bidders, buyers or sellers on our sites or other sites throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. SpaceElephant.com does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

### General

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this site. All amended terms automatically take effect 30 days after they are initially posted on the site. In addition, we will notify you through the SpaceElephant.com Message Center. If your questions are not answered online, you may write to us at: SpaceElephant.com Inc. Attn: Legal - Global Privacy Practices, Las Vegas, Nevada, write us at [admin@spaceelephant.com](mailto:admin@SpaceElephant.com)
